Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 11.06.20 15:40:59
布鲁克林 1983
当你成为一个青少年人的时候
When you first become a teenager,
因为你不在是一个小孩子了
you think it's cool to just be a teenager.
可是，很快你就明白
Then you find out no matter how cool you act,
无论你装得有多酷，其实一点也不酷
if you don't look cool,
除非你在长大5岁
you might as well be five years old.
当我13岁的时候，最酷的事情就是
And the coolest thing you could have when I was 13
穿皮甲克
was a leather jacket.
这小孩也许没有老爸， 可他有 皮 夹 克。
He might not have a daddy,
but he's got a leather jacket.
缇榭！
Keisha, you got a leather jacket, too?
你也弄了件皮甲克？
My mom just got it off layaway for me.
是啊，我妈给我的。
我真想也弄一件。
I was thinking about getting one.
你也准备弄一件？为什么？
You are? Why?
看看我?又瘦又小像个罗卜头？
Look at me. I'm skinny and I'm short.
只有穿上皮甲克才能装酷。
I'm not going to become cool overnight.
你也没有那么衰。
You don't look that bad, though.
但我还是应该武装起来。
Yeah, but I need something.
你想我穿皮甲克怎么样？
You think a leather jacket would help?
估计很帅。
I guess.
一件皮甲克绝对让我
All I was thinking is that
由罗卜头
the right leather jacket would have turned me from this guy...
变成大酷男
into this guy.
... 克里斯！
Chris. That leather jacket is cool.
你的皮甲克真酷！
有空我们一起玩。
Let's hang out.
摆几个POSE给你瞧瞧。
As soon as I'm finished posing.
怎样才能弄到那件皮甲克
I knew where to get a leather jacket.
我想我需要美圆
Now all I needed was money.
Transcript: Raceman - Trad: Birdyben Synchro/Relecture: Sixe
皮甲克？
A leather jacket?
要皮甲克干什么？
What do you need a leather jacket for?
缇榭 说皮甲克很酷。
Keisha said it was cool.
你认为皮甲克会让你变酷。
You think a leather jacket's going to make you cool?
这些家伙就是榜样
It made these guys gazillionaires.
当然可以
It could.
问题是，
The only thing is, I don't have $50.
我没有50美圆。
Just save up your allowance.
你可以把你的零用钱存起来。
My what?
什么？
Allowance. It's money.
零花钱， 你老爸每周给你的。
That your parents give you every week.
我听说过“零用钱”
I'd heard about allowances,
可我从来没有“见”过
but I didn't know they actually existed.
我以为那只是电视上才发生的事情
I thought it was just something that happened on TV.
给，儿子。
Here you go, son.
.1000美圆 谢谢老爸?
A thousand dollars.
Thank you, father.
自从我爸爸开始拼命工作
Since my father was always working,
他看上去总是心事重重
he always seemed kind of grumpy.
我们找不到机会开口要钱。
It seemed like there was never a good time to ask my father for money.
爸爸，可以给我15元，我可以去郊游。
Daddy, can I have $15 to go on a field trip
to the the Statue of Liberty?
好
Okay.
老爸，可以给我5圆钱看电影吗？
And, Dad, can I have $5 to go to the show?
好
Okay.
老公，给我25美圆逛街好吗？
Baby, can I get $25 to go shopping?
好
Okay.
看来这是我开口的黄金机会
It looks like this might be a good time after all.
老爸，
Hey, Dad?
我能要一件皮甲克吗？
Can I get a leather jacket?
皮甲克？
A leather jacket?
你有钱买吗？
You got some leather-jacket money?
你要皮甲克干什么?
Well, what do you need a leather jacket for?
朱尔的旧衣服不是挺好吗？
What's wrong with Drew's old coat?
以前，朱尔穿我的衣服。
Instead of Drew wearing my old clothes,
现在,我穿朱尔的衣服
I wore his old clothes.
谁叫我发育迟缓呢！
I think I was the first kid to get hand-me-ups.
太小了。
It's too small,
过时了。
it's out of style,
又不酷。
and it's just not cool.
穿衣服不是为了装酷，
It ain't supposed to be cool.
而是为了保暖。
It's supposed to be warm.
保暖就足够了。
Being warm is cool.
我不是要你出钱。
I'm not asking you to buy it.
我自己存钱。
I'll save up.
存什么钱？
Save up what?
存你给我零花钱？
I was hoping you can give me an allowance.
我知道这个要求很白痴。
I know it sounded like an innocent enough question,
真想出现这样的情况
but here's what he heard.
你每天象奴隶一样工作，
Since you work like a slave all day
却没有机会花钱，
and don't have any time to enjoy your own money,
不如，我帮你花。
can I have it?
我不会给你这个无所事事的臭小子一分钱。
I'm not giving you money for walking around doing nothing.
零花钱？！
An allowance?
我让你睡在我家里，
I'll allow you to sleep here at night.
我允许你吃我的土豆
I'll allow you to eat them potatoes.
我允许你用我的电灯。
I'll allow you to use my lights.
我允许你喝我的汽水。
I'll allow you to drink my Kool-Aid.
我允许你吃我的绿豆……
I'll allow you to nibble on them green beans.
我允许你看我的电视
I'll allow you to look at that TV.
我允许你用我的煤气
I'll allow you to run up my gas bill.
我允许你在我家里晃悠
I'll allow you to walk up my stairs.
我允许你向我提出这样荒谬的要求
I'll allow you to ask me these ridiculous-ass questions.
你还指望我给你零用钱？
Why should I give you an allowance
你做的一起都是我在买单。
when I already paid for everything you do?
你见过谁有零用钱？
Who you know that gets an allowance?
Huh?
训话完毕！
I'm finished.
格根就有零用钱。 他老爸每周给他5元。
I was talking to Greg and
he said that he gets five dollars a week.
听起来，他老爸比我厚道，
Sounds like Greg's doing better than me.
你就找他老爸要钱去吧，
Ask him for an allowance.
你想买皮甲克，
You want to buy a leather coat,
你必须自己挣钱。
you  need to get a leather-coat job.
老爸不在家的时候，
While things might have been tight with my father,
老妈很休闲。
my mother was getting loose.
独自在家的时候，她总是很开心，
She was always happy when she had the house to herself.
看看小报
She caught up on her reading.
煲煲电话
She talked on the phone.
偷吃很贵的零食，还是背着我们藏起来的。
She  ate expensive candy she hid from us.
但总有一些意想不到的事情打断她……
But there was one thing that she never counted on to mess up her day.
请进
Coming...
你们回来干什么？
What are y'all doing here?
学校有出了点事。
Something went wrong at our school.
关于铅涂料。
Something about the paint.
... 瘃怿 徕祆 " " .鲠?漕腴?蝈豇?/i>
Before vending machines were put into schools,
饿着肚子的孩子就像吃薯片一样吃掉它
hungry kids often snacked on lead paint chips.
味道好极了
Mmm.
This is good!
如果不是嘴馋，我们不会吃这些“特种材料”。
If we had ladders, he'd have ate the asbestos.
I want one! Me, too! Me, too!
给我留一点?
Me, too! Come on, me too!
等学校处理好之后，我们才能回去。
So we can go back after they finish repainting our classrooms.
好。乖乖的，我刚打扫干净。
All right, well, y'all stay out of my way,
一整天，我们干什么？
cause I'm cleaning up.
What are we going to do all day?
随便
I don't know.
自己玩吧
Go play.
在4:30之前，别弄乱了房子。
But you all better not mess up my house till after 4:30!
现在的小孩子，
I mean, asbestos kills,
连涂料也吃?
a little paint ain't gonna hurt.
他们回来之后，
After a day out of school,
老妈就找不到乐趣了。
my mother wasn't having any fun.
塔尼亚和朱尔也挺无聊
And neither were Tonya and Drew.
你在干什么？ 看漫画
- What are you doing? - Nothing.
当黑人小孩无聊的时候，
When broke kids get bored,
我们就玩那个流传很久的不用花钱的游戏
they play one of the cheapest games ever invented:
“赌你不敢！"
"I Dare You."
我赌你不敢把这些冰放到衣服里。
I dare you to put these ice cubes under your armpit.
赌多久?
For how long?
一分钟
One minute.
Okay.
1…… 2……
Whoo!
One...
two...
数得太慢了，塔尼亚。
Count it normal, Tonya...
3…… 你们两个小鬼在干什么？
three...
我赌他不敢把冰放到衣服里。
Girl, what is wrong with you?
I dared him to put ice cubes under his arms.
把冰拿出来，笨蛋。
Take the ice cubes from under your arm.
别放到杯子里，
Not... in the glass.
我们还要喝水呢。
Boy, people got to drink from that.
呵呵，我赌你不敢喝。
Okay, I dare you to drink it.
千万别喝? 很脏。
You better not. That's nasty.
我不喝。
I'm not.
不要赌这些无聊的东西。
You know what? Since you all want to dare so bad,
不如赌你们谁能安静坐着别惹事。
why don't y'all dare each other
to sit down and act like y'all got some sense?
不难办到吧。
How about that?
很高兴你们能安静的待在家里。
Boy, I'll be glad when y'all go back to school.
你们让我感觉很无聊。
You are driving me up the wall.
相 当 无聊！
Two walls.
你必须喝了。
Now you have to do something.
太脏了。
That's nasty.
同一时刻，这地球上最衰的男孩 也弄了件皮甲克
Meanwhile, I felt like the only guy on earth without a leather jacket.
－你也弄了件皮甲克? －帅呆了吧?
You got a leather jacket?
我老爸大发慈悲，给我买了皮甲克。
Cool, huh?
My dad got it for me at the army surplus store.
你这个家伙不是说皮甲克很衰的吗？
Hey, weren't you the one who said that leather didn't make you cool?
嘿嘿，看来我错了。
Yeah, but I was wrong.
你老爸同意给你零用钱了？
So, what did your dad say about an allowance?
他用了两个小时，
He said no... for about two hours.
来告诉我 没门。
Hi, Greg.
嗨！格莱格? 很帅的皮甲克！
Nice jacket.
连她也跟你说话了。
Wait. She's talking to you?
帅吧！
Cool, huh?
这让我买皮甲克的决心更坚定！
I got to get me a leather jacket.
十三岁的孩子很难找工作。
Finding a job when you're 13 is not the easiest thing to do.
找容易的工作……
I applied for easy jobs...
我为什么要把工作给你， 不就是往袋子里装东西。
Now why would I pay you to put groceries in a bag
我自己就可以搞定了。
when I can put them in a bag my damn self?
找困难的工作……
I applied for hard jobs...
想做保安？
Security guard, huh?
以前开过枪吗?
You ever been shot?
看来，我必须试试那些“计划外”的工作
I even applied for jobs I didn't know I was applying for.
有工作经验吗?
You any good with matches?
我只要经验丰富的人材。
There's a new barber down the block.
等你有了经验再来吧。
He needs to be taught a lesson.
我赌你不敢用背滑下楼梯。
I dare you to slide down the stairs on your back.
给我毛巾。
Give me the towel.
哇，看来躲在家里玩也和在布鲁克林街头一样
The only place more dangerous than the streets of Brooklyn
都有生命危险。
were the hallways of Brooklyn.
经历这么多挫败之后
After running out of options,
我只能指望一个人，可以帮我找到工作
I could only think of one person that could help me find work.
Hey.
爸，能帮我弄一份工作吗?
Dad, can you help me get a job?
什么？
- What? - I want to get a leather jacket.
我非常想买皮甲克。
我试过了，可是到现在还是找不到工作。
And I've been trying to get a job, but it's not working out so far.
你是认真的？
You  want it that bad, huh?
对
Yeah.
不如跟着我混？
Want to come and work with me?
－真的？ －不假。
- For real? - Yeah. Tomorrow's Saturday.
到周末了，你可以帮我送报纸。
You can come do deliveries with me.
我几个小时后回来。 3:30在楼下等我。
I'll be back in a few hours.
Now  be downstairs at 3:30.
－最迟3:31。 －我一定早到。
Not 3:31.
Don't worry. I'll be down early.
你不可能早到。
No such thing as early.
只要不迟到就可以了。
You're either on time or you're late.
终于朝我朝思暮想的皮甲克， 迈出了第一步。
I was committed to getting that jacket.
一切都是想起来简单，
Nothing was going to stop me.
做起来很难。
Nothing except a nap.
我以为老爸对我爽约会非常生气。
I thought my father would be really mad that I missed work.
看来，一件皮甲克变成一顿“皮鞭”
Instead of getting a leather jacket,
I thought I was going to get a leather belt.
你早上怎么了？
- What happened to you this morning? - I overslept.
我睡过头了。
你为什么不上来弄醒我？
How come you didn't come get me?
是你想要找工作，
You the one want the job.
工作可不会去找你。
Job ain't gonna wait for you.
这两位还在玩游戏
In the game of Dare, there are no rules,
不用守规则，不用循规蹈矩。只要胆大如牛就够了。
there are no regulations
and the game doesn't end till somebody's dead.
赌你不敢喝。
I dare you.
有什么好处？
What you going to give me?
2美圆
Two dollars.
快喝……
Drink it. Hurry up.
快喝……托尼亚。
Hurry up, Tonya.
快喝……
More. Drink it.
酷！
Cool.
味道如何？
How was it?
交出两美圆
Give me my two dollars.
第二天，我起来很早。
The next morning, I was up earlier than a Marine with a paper route.
咖啡？
Coffee?
走进老爸工作的地方，
Working with my father was mind-blowing.
我不敢相信，这里非常大，非常吵
I couldn't believe how big it was,
how loud it was.
一起都运作的很快！
How fast everything was going.
我就像是走进维加斯的流浪儿童
I felt like an Amish kid in Vegas.
来。
乔治！
What's up, George?
你好，荷特！
Hey, Herc.
- What's up? - All right.
这是谁？
Who's this?
我儿子克里斯。
That's my son, Chris.
谁是荷特?
Who's Herc?
荷特就是大力神，
Herc like Hercules.
那个强壮的人。
That's a strong man.
我只知道老妈给老爸起了个小名。
The only other names I knew my father by
were the words my mother called him,
原来老爸在这里也有个小名
and they didn't have nothing to do with being strong.
你也是荷特？
So, little Herc.
有你老爸风趣吗？
You funny like your old man?
我老爸很风趣？
My father's funny?
也不是那么风趣？
Ah, he ain't that funny.
是啊，我比你们这两个小子风趣多了。
Funnier than you two corny...
Oh!
老爸从来不抱怨
My father never cursed at home,
可在这里，他的抱怨很多
so hearing him curse at the job made me feel like I was in a secret club.
我好像置身于“诉苦”俱乐部
Get to work before I bring your mama back in here.
Yeah, okay, whatever you say.
See you, Little Herc.
You don't want me to tell your mama to come back here, too, man.
我们开始工作吧。
Hey, let's get to work.
自从老爸被老妈镇压以后。
I haven't heard cursing like that since my father stepped on my mother's bunion.
他从没敢在家里这样抱怨。
在家里，游戏刚刚结束， 麻烦却开始了。
At home, the Dare game was over,
but  the trouble was just starting.
你怎么了？宝贝。
What's wrong, baby?
我在房间里听见你好像不对劲。
I heard you moaning all the way from my room.
我的胃疼。
My stomach hurts really bad.
让我看看。
Let me feel.
糟糕，你有点发烧。
Oh, no. You're burning up.
让我看看你的肚子。
Let me feel your tummy.
我要带你去急诊室。
Okay, baby, I'm gonna take you to the emergency room.
等着，我去给你那衣服。
Wait here. I'm gonna get your coat.
朱尔，起床。
Drew, get up!
只有发生了非常严重的情况 我们才去看医生。
Going to the doctor was serious business,
通常情况下，我们得了小伤小病，
because usually, if something was wrong with one of us,
老爸，老妈认为， “云南白药”包治百病。
my parents thought they could fix it with Robitussin.
啊！
Ow!
我的手指受伤了。
I burned my finger!
让我看看。
Let me see, boy, let me see.
我给你上点“云南白药”。
Take some Robitussin.
嘴里有两个泡泡。
Looks like a tooth broke off.
我去拿“云南白药”。
Yeah. I'll go get the Robitussin.
妈，
What?
克里斯被车撞了。
Mama, Chris just got hit by a car.
哦，我的老天。我马上去拿“云南白药”。
Oh, my God, I'll go get the Robitussin.
我不会告诉她。
I'm not telling her.
是你自己要喝的。
You're the one who drank it.
是你赌我不敢喝。
You dared me!
小声点。
Shh. Be quiet.
来吧，我们走。
Okay, come on. Let's go.
外面真冷啊。
It was cold outside.
我很累，这些报纸就像有千斤重。
I was tired, and those papers were heavy.
为了买那件皮甲克，我必须忍辱负重。
I was starting to wonder if that leather jacket was worth it.
HI，克里斯。
Hey, Chris.
什么时候才能做完?
What time you getting off?
差的远呢。我必须付清买皮甲克的钱。
Never.
I got to pay off this jacket.
OK，搞定了。 好啊。
Okay, that's it.
我们能休息一下吗？
Good. Now can we have a break?
天亮前，我们没有时间休息。
We won't get a break for another three hours.
走吧。
Come on.
急诊室
在电视上，我们看到
If you watch TV, you know that an emergency room
急诊室是世界上最繁忙的地方。
is one of the most exciting places you can be.
可这是骗人的。
Wrong.
Yeah, Charlie and Karen. They broke up.
- What about Charlie? - Well, he went back to New York.
打断一下，护士。 我女儿的胃快要疼死了。
Excuse me, nurse. My baby's stomach is killing her.
想想看，在急诊室工作的人
The thing about people who work in emergency rooms
每天都待在空空的急诊室里
is they're not the ones with the emergency-- you are.
爽 啊 ！
Really? But did you see Tracy last week with her new man?
难道你没有看到我和我受伤的孩子站在这里?
Do you see me standing here with a sick child?
难道你没有看到我正和别人说话？
Do you see me here talking to somebody?
我他妈受够了你们这些鸟人，
Quit hollerin' at people!
我他妈不干了。反正我的男人打三份工。
You know, I don't need this. My man has three jobs!
成为老爸的同事，
Being at work with my father
这是我做过的最酷的事情。
was one of the coolest things I ever did.
我们闯红灯
We broke laws...
糟糕，糟糕，减速……
Hey, hey, we can make it!
Hold on, man. Here we go.
Let's go! Let's go!
Whoo!
Yeah!
踢别人的“屁股”。
Curse people out.
快开！
Hurry up! Let's go!
从我前面滚开。
Get out of the way!
你还是做跟屁虫吧！
Kiss my ass! That's right!
跟在我后面闻臭屁……
那是我经历过的最让人兴奋的晚上。
That's right!
That was one of the most exciting nights of my life.
我们送报纸到布鲁克林。
We delivered papers in Brooklyn.
送报纸去皇后大道。
We delivered papers in Queens,
意大利人的地盘，中国人的地盘
Little Italy, Chinatown,
西班牙人的地盘。
Spanish Harlem,
波多黎各人的地盘
Puerto Rican Harlem, the Bronx,
法国人的地盘……
Greenwich Village.
甚至是没有人读报纸的地方。
We delivered papers to people I didn't even know could read.
这一趟要把报纸送到15个地方，
And after delivering more than 15 tons worth of newspapers,
累得我只想叫娘。
all I could think was "Where the hell is the sun?"
第36号，准备去见医生。
Um,  number 36, the doctor will see you now.
不，不，不，这真是荒谬。
Oh, no, no, no!
Come on! This is ridiculous!
谁来看看我的女儿?
Who's going to help my baby?
那个男人中了子弹。
That man's been shot.
我女儿虽然没有中弹，但这不代表她不疼。
Well, just because she's not shot doesn't mean she isn't hurt.
如果她的伤很轻，
If this wasn't an emergency,
我们也不会出现在这里。
we wouldn't have to come to the emergency room.
如果你再不让她进病房，
Look, if she doesn't get to see a doctor,
我就让你“爬”进病房。
we're going to have to get you a doctor.
想试试吗？
Yeah, now.
现在！
很抱歉让你们等了很久。
I'm sorry it took you so long to get in.
因为刚才有人威胁要踢护士的屁股。
It's about time somebody threatened to kick that nurse's ass.
嗯，看来我们必须进行测试。
Mm, I think we have to run some tests.
什么测试？
What kind of tests?
首先，要验血。小女士。
Well, first we need to draw some blood, little lady.
稍等……
I'll be right back.
――嗯…… ――必须进行测试，
Mama, I don't want...!
Baby, you have to take the test in order for youto feel better.
――这样，你才能好过来。 ――妈……
Mom, uh...
我必须对你坦白。
I have to tell you something.
什么？
What?
是我让塔尼亚喝了一些“麻辣饮料”。
I dared Tonya to drink a hot sauce shake.
“麻辣饮料”？
A hot sauce shake?
我的女儿，你怎么这么傻？
Girl, what in the world would you do that for?
他赌我不敢喝。
He dared me!
医生，我认为没有必要测试了。
Doctor, I don't think that'll be necessary.
她只是喝了一些麻辣饮料。
My son dared her to drink a hot sauce shake.
麻辣饮料？
A hot sauce shake?
..酱油、醋、牛奶……
Yeah, you know, vinegar, hot sauce, syrup and milk.
我没想到这会让人生病。
I didn't know it'd make her that sick.
我明白了。
I know what to do.
给。
Here.
写的什么？
- What is this? - Ipecac.
.嚅赭圜
This is to induce vomiting.
.驿 忮
做完之后，她可能会有些轻微的咳嗽。
When she's done, she may have a slight cough.
.
Give her some Robitussin.
你会好的。
She'll be fine.
...
Ain't no fussin' with the 'Tussin.
... 嚅?铤蝰鏖? 蝽 澍遽殍羼轱
Ow!
朱立业斯。
Julius,
你要把卡车开进来。
you got to take that truck back over to DeKalb.
明天做好吗？
- I'll do it tomorrow. - No, I need it done now.
不行，现在就要。
难道你就不能找别人做？
You can't find somebody else?
我为什么要找别人做？
Why should I find somebody else? I found you.
我现在就找到你，
I want that truck back over to DeKalb now.
我要你现在就去做。
原来，我以为只有一个人能指挥老爸：
The only person I ever saw tell my father what to do was my mother.
我老妈
老爸，你就让他这么嚣张？
Dad, you just going to let him tell you what to do?
人在屋檐下，不得不低头。
Either that or I won't have nothing to do.
去做吧。
Come on.
Ow.
酸啊。
That hurt.
我们谈谈。
You worked hard.
好。
Yeah.
感觉还不错吧。
Feels kind of good, though, don't it?
是啊。
Yeah.
终于熬过苦难。
After everything I'd been through,
现在老爸将给我工钱了。
I understood my father a lot more.
工作的那么辛苦，
Because when you work that hard,
熬出头不容易。
you think about every dime you spend.
好在，马上就要发财啦！
And I was thinking about how I was going to spend mine.
25$
$25?
是。
That's right.
付出多少，收获多少。
You earned every penny.
没有不劳而获的事情。
Don't forget to ice down your arms.
可是那皮甲克要50元。
But I need $50 for the jacket.
你想要的，和你能得到的，
No, you don't. You want $50.
这是两码事情。
There's a difference.
我求你给我买甲克的时候， 你要我去工作。
When I asked you for the jacket, you said I should get a job.
现在，我做了工作……
And I got a job.
你做的还不够。
Job didn't pay enough.
好啦，25元也不少啊。
You got $25.
我一次挣25元钱，还是在30岁那年。
I didn't make my first $25 till I was 30 years old.
多不容易啊。
And I still got two of 'em.
想想，
Look, you want the jacket, save your money.
你想买甲克。
你就必须继续存钱。
You can work with me again next week.
下周还和我一起工作吗?
好吧。
Okay.
再见，妈妈。
- Bye, Mommy. - See ya.
再见。
Have a good day at school.
在学校过得愉快点。
几天后，
A few days later, Drew and Tonya were back in school
朱尔和塔尼亚回学校了。
老妈又可以过她的快乐生活。
and my mother could go back to her routine.
从没有见过一个女人这么快乐！
I never seen a woman so happy to clean.
同时，我还在一边工作一边存钱。
Meanwhile, I was still wishing that my job had worked out a little better.
终于有天，我存够了钱。
After all I'd gone through with my father,
谢天谢地，终于可以买皮甲克了。
I appreciated him that much more.
你好，我喜欢我的甲克。
Hi, man.
你也弄了一件。
- How do you like my jacket? - You got that one?
这是打折的最后一件。
I got the last one on sale.
看来，我起早贪黑的打工，都是白做了。
But I didn't go out in the middle of the night
and do all that work for nothing.
可分期付款
六个月后
穿这么多不热吗？
Aren't you hot in that thing?
别这样说，我很好。
Please. I'm fine.
克里斯！
Chris?!
本集结束，下周见！
Raceman/Sixe/Birdyben FOROM.COM